here are five lessons that I've learned
as I've started and continued on the
journey of saving the world number one
put your ideas out there into the real
world it will grow and change as it
encounters the world it can only be so
perfect
before you release it to the world and
the world breaks it and then you repair
it and the world breaks it and you
repair it and that process makes you
stronger makes your idea stronger and
gives you a path of receipts of what
you've been through and gives the world
that number to put yourself out there if
you're not willing to put your face and
your name to your idea
it can't gain the traction that it that
it deserves in order for us to be able
to trust an idea unless you have
millions of dollars for marketing you
are the message and so you have to be
willing to put yourself out there which
brings us to number three which is do
the best job you can now you don't need
to be perfect you could stumble on your
words you don't need good camera
equipment you don't need to have your
your wording exactly right depending on
whether it's it's video or text done is
better than perfect what can you do
right now I don't think I do the best
job on these videos of me talking into
the camera and imagining who imagining
an audience I am talking to
I do much better in conversations and so
that was very obvious to me years ago
yet how could I save the world with
conversation ridiculous right what I can
do is show up and have a conversation
with anyone about their idea I can show
up and have a conversation about any
topic that is meaningful to me and any
world-changing topic it's making 'full
to me and that is what I am doing with
the idea cafe with our project raisins
solution raisings I get to engage in
these conversations that are actually
going to save the world and that is what
I could do what you can do is gonna be
very different
I also offer you to do what is safe and
easy for you that is what I needed to
have happen and society says that's not
okay you have to do what it's hard and
you have to do what feels risky and I
couldn't do that and so I was always
doing the adjacent possible of and still
AM of what feels safe and easy and in so
doing I've grown faster and further than
I ever did before when I was pushing
myself
number four yeah I'm like are we on
number four did I ever say number four
have fun this is hard work
and it is a marathon it is not a sprint
so what can you do in sustain it and
keep reevaluating it and feel does it
feel right to you is this as it for me
anyway as it becomes hard and arduous
and I feel like it's a have to instead
of a get to I have to reevaluate what
I'm doing and so but you can you look
back on my dad a little Channel and
he'll be constant oh I'm gonna do this
thing for thirty days and ten days in I
stopped doing it and it's because it
stops resonating with me and then I
introduce the next thing in the next
thing and I'm figuring out what works
for me
number five learning comes from
everywhere as you are putting your idea
and yourself out in the world you're
going to encounter people and their
ideas and as both the people and the
ideas bring up emotion in you whether
positive or negative if emotions can be
either of those things I don't I think
they're all positive anger sadness
frustration envy I have learned so much
so deeply from those emotions just if
not more than I've learned from things
like love and gratitude and hope because
as I encounter people and their ideas
I'm willing to learn what I'm there to
learn for me and my ideas I am so
grateful to get to be alive right now at
this moment in history and to get to be
part of creating a better world and the
be the world that I envisioned after my
game because I definitely don't own game
B is a world that everyone can
participate in creating their best life
and we can find our groups find our
people to be able to come together and
create solutions that there can be
overarching world solutions that we can
we can choose to be a part of we can
create a better world for everyone and I
this YouTube channel is me sharing that
journey and these are five lessons I
have learnt along the way that hopefully
help you if you have ideas that you know
are world-changing and we're gonna help
us move from where we currently are to a
world that works for everyone an omni
win ante rivalry society that we can all
thrive in and we can all gain we can all
benefit from having everybody else
living in that world as well a world of
invitation instead of forcing so this is
today's video please like and subscribe
hit that little bell so you can know
when I come up with my next world-saving
idea or nest GPS link or next moments of
my life that I am sharing as I go
through this journey thank you